Jeff Hogg

Napa, CA (707) 287-2123 <u>JeffHogg86@gmail.com</u> <u>LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio | HackerRank</u>

Summary

Full-stack Developer with a background in broadcast communications. While attending UC Berkeley's Full-stack Web Development program, I gained hands-on experience developing and deploying web applications, manipulating data, and solving algorithms.

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: React, Redux, TypeScript, Node.js, Express

Databases: MongoDB, MySQL

Projects

Iron Dojo

A react/redux web application to track your strength and conditioning sessions. Technologies: Front-end design/Material-UI, Routing, API's, Google Oauth, Final Form

Netflix clone

A Netflix clone built with React and Redux. Deployed with Firebase.

Technologies: RESTful API's, CSS

Discord clone

A Discord clone built with React and Redux. Deployed with Firebase.

Technologies: Google Oauth, Redux, CSS

Experience

Cisco - *Technical Director*

2013 - PRESENT

- Video playback, create graphics, power point, manage records
- Operate video switchers and cameras

IATSE - Technical Director

2012 - PRESENT

- Direct, camera operate, video switch
- Live sports video board and television broadcasts

Education

University of California, Berkeley - Certificate, Full-stack Web Development	2020
San Francisco State University - Bachelor of Arts, Broadcast Communications	2010-2012
Napa Valley College - Associate of Science, Broadcast Engineering	2007-2009